http://1049theriver.com/privacy-policy

Press enter to begin your search
River Radio Ministries
Privacy PolicyHere's a long, long, long ramble about what we do or don't do with your information! We welcome any questions and comments you may have, so please don't hesitate to reach out to us. The River Radio Ministries Privacy Policy was last updated December 2018.
Contact Us
At the River we understand your privacy is important to you. Even though we may need to collect information about you to provide some of the products and services we offer, you may not want us to disclose that information to others. We respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected from you. Accordingly, what follows is a description of how we use the information we collect about you (collectively “Your Information”). Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to sites maintained by River and its subsidiaries, and not to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact River at the email address specified on the Website.
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. WHEN YOU USE OUR WEBSITE YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
Will River Radio Ministries Disclose the Information It Collects to Outside Parties?
Yes. Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, River Radio Ministries does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. However, River Radio Ministries may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information to third-party vendors. These statistics will include no personally identifying information. River Radio Ministries may also release Your Information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with the law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of our Terms of Use or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of River Radio Ministries, our users, or others. Also, some or all of Your Information may be turned over to third-party vendors who assist us in fulfilling some of the functions of this Web site. Finally, we may provide Your Information to third parties if you authorize us to.
What Information Do We Collect? How Do We Use It?
| Voluntary Information
Surveys
Sometimes River Radio Ministries posts optional surveys in which we ask for personally identifiable information. Here are some ways we might use that information:
To send you information about the River and this Web site
To give to our content partners, who may send you promotional material
To give to our advertisers, who may send you information about their products and services
The choice is yours — you don’t have to answer surveys, but if you do, please understand that the information you provide will be used by River Radio Ministries and may be provided to third parties. If we’re asking for optional information, we may mark it with an asterisk (*) so you know you can skip it if you want.
Contests and Sweepstakes
From time to time River Radio Ministries runs contests and sweepstakes in which we ask for personally identifiable information such as your name, age, email address or telephone number. That’s so we can determine if you’re eligible for the contest and to let you know if you win. Sometimes we request additional information such as your gender, marital status and income level. Here are some of the ways we might use the information that we collect:
• To determine if you’re eligible for the contest
• To notify you if you’re a winner
• To send you information about River Radio Ministries and this web site
• To give to content partners, who may send you promotional email
• To give to advertisers, who may send you email about their products and services
We may share aggregate information with our partners and advertisers.
What About “Cookies”?
”Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your Web browser on your computer’s hard drive. From time to time our Web site may place cookies on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use our site.
Links to Other Sites
When you visit River Radio Ministries, you may be linked to other outside sites. This includes links to sites operated by advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use our logo as part of an agreement with River Radio Ministries. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. These other sites are not subject to the River Radio Ministries Privacy Policy and River Radio Ministries is not responsible for the privacy policies of these other sites, nor for the use of any information that these sites may collect. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the Website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Third Party Services
Users may register for other services from our Website. Certain products and/or services available on our Website are provided to you in partnership with third parties’ and may require you to disclose personally identifiable information in order to register for and access such products and/or services. Such products and/or services shall identify the third party partners at the point of registration. If you elect to register for such products and/or services, your personally identifiable information will be transferred to such third parties’ and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third parties’. We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of such third parties’ and, therefore, you should review the privacy practices and policies of such third parties’ prior to providing your personally identifiable information in connection with such products and/or services.
Service Providers
We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.
Law Enforcement
We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of River or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.
Business Transfers
We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.
Children’s Privacy
Naturally, the safety of children is very important to us. River Radio Ministries will not knowingly accept personal information from children under the age of 13 without obtaining parental consent.
Trademarks
River Radio Ministries, its websites and other graphics, logos, page headers, button icons, scripts, and service names are trademarks, registered trademarks or trade dress of River Radio Ministries in the U.S. and/or other countries. River Radio Ministries’ trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not River’s, in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers or in any manner that disparages or discredits River Radio Ministries. All other trademarks not owned by River that appear on this site are the property of their respective owners, who may or may not be affiliated with, connected to, or sponsored by River Radio Ministries.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitation of Liability
THIS SITE AND ALL INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) AND SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED BY RIVER ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS, UNLESS OTHERWISE SPECIFIED IN WRITING, RIVER MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THIS SITE OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) OR SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THIS SITE, UNLESS OTHERWISE SPECIFIED IN WRITING. YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THIS SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK.
TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW, RIVER DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. RIVER DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THIS SITE; INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) OR SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THIS SITE; THEIR SERVERS; OR EMAIL SENT FROM IVER ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. RIVER WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE OR FROM ANY INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) OR SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THIS SITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, UNLESS OTHERWISE SPECIFIED IN WRITING.
CERTAIN STATE LAWS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN DAMAGES. IF THESE LAWS APPLY TO YOU, SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS, OR LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, AND YOU MIGHT HAVE ADDITIONAL RIGHTS.
Applicable Law
By visiting our website, you agree that the laws of the State of Ohio, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Terms of Service and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and River Radio Ministries.
In Summary
We understand your privacy is important to you. We do not sell, trade, or rent Your Information to others subject to the provisions listed above. If you never want to receive any announcements or special offers from us, send us an email at: comments@riverradio.com
. Remember to list each of the email accounts you have given us.
Your Consent
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of Your Information by River Radio Ministries as set forth in this Privacy Policy. River Radio Ministries may at any time amend, modify, restate or revise this Privacy Policy by updating this posting, and you should therefore periodically visit this page to determine the then current Privacy Policy that is in effect.
Tell Us What You Think
We welcome your questions and comments about privacy. If you have any questions or feel we are not abiding by this Privacy Policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (614) 289-5700 or via email: contact@riverradio.com.
881 E. Johnstown Road Gahanna 43230 | 614-289-5700 | © River Radio Ministries |  Privacy Policy | EEO Report | FCC Public Files | License Renewal Applications
LISTEN LIVE
104.9 the River
89.3 the River Newark
89.3 the River Chillicothe
90.9 the River Lancaster
Podcasts
DONATE
DJ’s
